Larry Maschhoff

NewGate Capital Partners

lmaschhoff@gmail.com

Summary

I bring 40 years of business and banking experience, 3 years experience as manager of the Center for Emerging Entrepreneurs a business incubator and business accelerator program at Illinois State University, 1 year experience in manufacturing at Nascote Industries to NewGate Capital Partners.

I spent most of my career in the banking industry as the President of three banks. In addition, I was active serving as Chairman and board member of The Illinois Community Bankers Association; I served on the Board of Directors for the Independent Community Bankers Association and I was Chairman of their Regulation Committee. As a member of these organizations, I was active in lobbying state, national and governmental regulatory organizations.

I was also the hired as an Administrative Manager of Nascote Industries. In that position I helped form a new joint venture between Ford Motor Co. and Magna International, a Canadian auto parts manufacturing company,

I hold a B.S. in Business Administration from Southern Illinois University in Edwardsville, IL., and have participated and graduated from seven banking schools through five Universities: University of Colorado at Boulder CO., Oklahoma University at Norman, OK., Louisiana State University, Baton Rouge, LA., Illinois State University, and Southern Illinois University at Carbondale.

Specialties: banking, financial statements, commercial loans, commercial real estate loans, small business loans, bank loan requirements, angel investors, creating usable financial statement; business consulting

Experience

Partner at NewGate Capital Partners, LLC February 2015 - Present

Partner

2013 - Present

Managing Director at Center for Emergng Entrepreneurs - Illinois State University June 2010 - September 2013 (3 years 4 months)

Center for Emerging Entrepreneurs, the CEE actively helped business grow through coaching, mentoring, and direct services. The CEE provided individualized business help and consulting services to each client.

I was hired in June of 2010 to start a business incubator program for ISU and the EDC in our community. The incubator was formally launched in February 2011 as The Center for Emerging Entrepreneurs.

As part of our services, we provided:

- 1. assistance in helping a business create solid business feasibility study or business plan.
- 2. review company performance to evaluate and recommend strategies for potential growth
- 3. referrals to local business resources.
- 4. educational seminars and workshops.
- 5. coaching and mentoring for start up businesses
- 6. consulting services to existing business to help them grow and prosper.

Chairman and President

August 1987 - March 2010 (22 years 8 months)

- Increased assets from \$39,000,000 to \$240,000,000
- Formed a holding company and purchased the bank in 1993
- Managed 49 bank staff and all bank functions (investments, lending, deposits, operations, marketing, and trust)
- · Chairman of the Board of Directors
- Active in state and national banking legislative and regulation issues
- Active in many local community and economic development issues

CEO and President

1988 - 1990 (3 years)

Community Bank of Galesburg was an affiliate of the Bank Holding Company which owned the Bank of Illinois.

Administrative Manager

June 1986 - June 1987 (1 year 1 month)

- Directed all administrative activities for a new joint venture between Ford Motor Co. and Magna International
- Managed the hiring for all administrative staff
- Directed and developed a marketing, costing, and sales program
- Managed the joint venture issues between two large corporations
- Directed and managed all accounting functions

President

October 1969 - June 1986 (16 years 9 months)

Education

Southern Illinois University, Edwardsville
BS, Business Administration and Accounting, 1971 - 1975
Illinois State University
Louisiana State University
Southern Illinois University, Carbondale
University of Colorado at Boulder
Banking
University of Oklahoma
Banking

Larry Maschhoff

NewGate Capital Partners

Imaschhoff@gmail.com



Contact Larry on LinkedIn